过去可出过不少意外
We've had some incidents in the past.
你都不会相信我们经手的一些案件 就是
Oh, you wouldn't believe some of the cases we've had. Just...
员工发色情短信 在公司电脑上看黄片
Employees sexting and porn on their work computers,
在办公室里手淫 太恶心了
masturbating in the office. Just disgusting.
- 真恶心 - 是啊 真恶心
- Disgusting. - Yeah, disgusting.
你说买这些底裤的人要是知道
Don't you think the people buying these panties
它们是由囚犯缝制的 他们不会觉得别扭吗
will feel weird if they knew a bunch of felons made them?
不会啊 他们没准还觉得很性感呢
Mmm-mmm. They'd probably think that shit was hot.
对 他们应该在标签上写 "联邦监狱制造"
Yeah, they should put that shit on the tag, "Made in Federal."
要是有男人知道这些涤纶破玩意儿
Dudes would be into polyester grannies